According to our records,
the Manga Club has not
qualified for full status for three years.
It wasn't a problem before because
there were open club rooms.
For three whole years?
You're the club president. How did you not know?
In any case,
we're going to give this room to them instead.
If you have any questions or concerns,
come talk with us in the Student Council Office.
We're going to lose our club room...
We Need an Advisor!
S-senpai?
Senpai?! Why are there stars circling your head?!
She cast Fuddle.
No time for debuffs, we have to think!
Cure Confusion!
The Final Fantasy system?!
That's right, we've got to think!
So, uh, w-what do we do?
I-if we lose our room,
what do we do with our stuff?
Or our books?!
We'll have to get the doujins
and figures outta here somehow...
But what do we do with all these books?!
W-we could donate them to the school library?
Our school library doesn't have a hentai section!
You're the club president. How did you not know?
This is all my fault.
If I'd been a better president...
Senpai!
We're only losing our room because
we're no longer a club, right?
So if we do something to remain a club,
then we might be able to stay here!
If this were a manga,
this is where the plot starts!
And when the going gets tough,
tough otaku get going!
Ririsa...
We'll do everything we can to stay, but...
But if we still get kicked out, then...
Then...
Then I hope you'll still stick around, Senpai.
I still want to fulfill my cosplay
dreams with you by my side!
Stop embarrassing yourself, Okumura!
She's counting on you!
Now things are getting interesting!
That's what Lord Ashford always
says when the party's in trouble!
Senpai!
I'm club president.
I've gotta do something to save our room!
Student Council Office
That would be correct.
If you satisfied the conditions for full club status,
then you could keep your room.
Really?!
We'd need you to write a report on your
club activities for us to review your status,
but before we can do any of that,
you need to have an active advisor.
So, we just need to find a teacher
who's willing to be that advisor?
Right, and when you do,
have them sign this form here.
If it helps,
here's a list of clubs
and their current advisors.
Later, I can get you some examples
of reports to model yours after.
Thanks for all the help.
I know I should've been better about all this.
Did you think we had it out for the Manga Club?
What? No, I didn't think that!
I mean, kinda...
We're just enforcing the rules.
We don't have any personal vendetta against you guys.
We're here to help everyone.
All you need to do is ask.
Feel free to stop in if you need anything else.
We just need a teacher...
Hello!
Advise your club?
I'm already busy with my other clubs, sorry!
Not when I've got another baby at home now.
Want to see a picture?
I need better work-life balance!
You don't need to oversee our meetings
or go to any competitions...
Sure, but putting my name down means more
paperwork and meetings I gotta deal with.
I'm guessing you didn't realize
advising a club was a lot of work.
Thanks, anyways.
Did I hear that right, Okumura-chan?
You're looking for a club advisor?
Yes, sir.
And having a hard time of it, too, huh.
Hanyuu-sensei is new,
so she's probably available.
Hanyuu-sensei?
Aww, you haven't met her yet?
She teaches Home Ec, and she's gorgeous!
You won't believe this, Mayuri-chan.
Wow, it sounds crazy.
I haven't even told you what it is yet!
I know...
And it's time for you to go off to your clubs.
Excuse me, are you Hanyuu-sensei?
Hmm. And you're asking me?
N-none of the other teachers are available.
I might've said yes in April,
but we're halfway through the semester now.
Yeah, and Mayuri-chan is busy enough!
Yeah, go figure...
Better luck next time, dude.
Darn.
Sorry I couldn't be of more help.
No, it's okay.
C'mon, boys, either go home or find a club!
Aww, c'mon.
What's wrong?
You look like you have something to say.
Oh, no, sorry!
Hmm?
I feel like I've seen her somewhere before...
Milky
Succubus
Oh...!
Milky Succubus!
"Milky" what?
Okumura-kun, right? Come with me.
Mayuri-chan?!
Okay, dipshit. How'd you find out?
S-so you ARE Mayura-sama!
Say that name again and you're dead.
Holy shit, she's scary!
Second chance. How'd you find out?
And be honest, or you're gonna find
out how sharp I keep my kitchen knife.
Oh, God!
S-sensei, please...
What? Need me to tell your parents you love them?
Please don't kill me!
They're touching me.
Your Milky bits.
Think you're funny, huh?!
P-please, hear me out!
Let me tell you about our club!
What?! Your club's focused on cosplay?!
That's so awesome.
Huh?
Um, I mean...
I knew I recognized her.
She's that middle-school student I met before.
I'd be happy to see her if it weren't so ironic...
Without our room,
Ririsa won't be able to keep cosplaying!
So please, May- uh, Hanyuu-sensei!
I'm sorry.
That's all the more reason for me to stay away.
Huh?
I've no right to show my face to her.
Not after I betrayed the world of cosplay.
What? Betrayed it how?
Did something bad happen?
No!
It's obvious! I'm a teacher now,
I can't do that kind of cosplay anymore!
Home Ec Workbook
If I were still selling DVDs with
half-naked pictures of myself,
I'd lose my job!
Y-yeah, that... That makes sense.
That's why I stopped.
There's no other reason.
So... so that's why I can't possibly face her now.
Mayura-sama...
Remember what I said about saying that name?!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I love cosplaying,
but I always knew I'd have to give it up someday.
So I had my fun,
but stayed focused on my career.
I made sure I went to a good high school
and college and became a public school teacher.
Can you blame me?!
Hello?! Why are you mad at me?!
I chose the coward's way out.
I was all ready to formally retire,
but when the time came,
I ghosted everyone instead.
I basically abandoned all my cosplay
friends and pretended I never did any of it.
I'm only here because I betrayed the cosplay world.
I've got no right to face her now.
You have to understand.
Even that didn't convince her...
Okay.
We'll let the other club have our room, then.
I'm sorry.
But then we have another problem.
I'm pretty sure somewhere in our clubroom
is a copy of Mayura-sama's cosrom.
What?! You have one, here, in that building?!
There's too much stuff in there to take it all home,
so we were thinking of giving stuff
away to anyone who wants it.
Who knows what would happen if
another student got their hands on it?
You little freak!
Are you blackmailing me?!
Sorry, Sensei!
This is the only way we can keep our clubroom!
I have to do this for Ririsa!
I found a teacher who might agree to advise us!!
I'll hear you out, but just this once!
I'm bringing her to the clubroom so we can talk to her
Yes, ma'am!
And you won't tell a soul my cosplay name!
Nice, Senpai!!
Roger that!!
WOW!!
R-right, I won't!
Ririsa! I brought...
I-I'm Ririsa Amano, I'm a first-year,
and I love cosplay!
I hope you'll be our new advisor!
Why didn't you change?!
I-I thought it might be better to let her see my cosplay!
I mean, yeah, maybe...
She's the pretty teacher I saw the other day!
You've grown into such an incredible otaku!
Sensei?
Liliel? A little outdated,
but still completely valid.
Did you make this yourself?
Your hems could use some work.
These details are nice.
I can tell you love her.
Sensei?!
Sensei, do you know a lot about cosplay?!
Absolutely not!
Yeah, she'll believe that.
But first, she needs to recognize you!
O-one of my friends is into cosplay.
Oh, that's cool!
There it is!
Milky
Succubus
My amazing but embarrassing first cosrom!
And they've left it out there right in the open!
Okumura, you little shit!
A... Amano-san, what's this?
I don't think this belongs at school-
Oh, that's my favorite cosrom of all time!
It's by Mayura-sama,
and you can tell how much she
loves her character, Lustalotte!
Every perfect detail and pose is overflowing
with the respect she has for the series.
She taught me how cosplay is a wonderful
avenue for showing your love for something!
I want to be on her level someday.
Y-you love her that much? You love... This?
She's my favorite cosplayer in the whole world!
I want to be just like her one day!
Sensei, if we want to keep cosplaying,
we need to have this clubroom.
Right! I forgot we were talking about that!
If you came on as our advisor,
we could keep it.
Is that all you wanted to discuss with me?
I agreed to hear you out,
and I've done that.
Besides, you shouldn't bring this to school.
I'll hold onto this for you.
Home Ec Lab
What the hell?!
Who was that precious cinnamon roll?!
An angel?! Did God send me an angel?!
I literally can't.
I want to hug her and squeeze her to death.
I want to be her Mom.
No, I could hug her all I wanted
and that wouldn't get her out of my head!
Wait, can I subscribe to her?
I'll pay for a premium sub, Ririsa Amano!
Now that I'm working full time,
I've got a higher limit on my credit card!
RIRISA
She's so perfect.
Do you still need something?
You can cut the act. I saw everything.
You don't know when to give up, do you?
I have to do this, for Ririsa.
Even if I come on as your advisor,
you might still lose your club room.
I'm not sure if you've heard about your club history.
Their old advisor Fujimoto-sensei took them
to the High School Manga Championship,
High School Manga Championship
and they apparently did really well every year.
That's why they got a clubroom.
With or without an advisor,
the two of you won't be able
to pass the report review.
You know, the old club members did mention that...
We'll figure something out!
I want to make sure Ririsa can keep cosplaying.
No, I want to make sure we
can keep cosplaying together!
Stubborn as a mule, aren't you.
I'm with you, though.
Sensei!
I also want to see more of her cosplays!
You're doing this for yourself!
Fine. You got me.
I'll turn in your report for you.
You mean it?!
But you have to do me a big favor, Okumura.
Get me a copy of her cosrom.
You can have as many as you want.
So now we write a report?
Yeah, but we definitely can't tell them
we're working on sexy photo collections.
Right. Sorry I can't help.
Hey, don't apologize! This isn't your fault!
Me and the other Manga Club
members created this mess.
We've just gotta think of a club
activity that'll make us sound legit!
Y-yeah, good idea!
We're the Manga Club,
so we could make our own manga.
Really?!
Would you draw one about Liliel?!
Yeah!
I've kinda always wanted
to draw a Liliel fan comic.
Especially a retelling of that
one scene from the main series...
I definitely want to see what you come up with!
I'll get to work, then!
Hanyuu-sensei!
How are things going?
Thank you so much for coming on as our advisor!
Okay, I've gotta go.
Don't take her with you!
I see...
So you're going to draw some manga?
Do you have any advice?
I might be your advisor,
but that doesn't mean I'll have advice.
Is this your draft?
Ash/Lili SFW romance, 24 pages?
These were big back in the day.
You'll want to finish your draft fast so you
can be ready to print the first week of July.
These days, you can just email stuff to the
printer and get it back right away for Comiket.
Sounds like you have a lot of advice.
Let's see here...
I mean, a doujinshi doesn't have to have stellar art...
I think your art is cute, Senpai!
No, this is a bust.
Guess not everyone can transform
their love into expressive works of art.
You're on another level, Ririsa.
You're doing what I always wanted
to do through your cosplay.
Senpai...
Anyways...
After-School Program
Seeking student volunteers
This came in today. Want to give it a go?
They want volunteers to come
afterschool and read to kids?
You two love manga, right?
Go read some to the kids. They'll love it.
And it counts as community service.
Let's go, Liliel!
Yes, Ashford-sama!
We'll summon every ounce of courage...
They're not listening at all.
Were we this rowdy when we were little?
I'm so sorry to waste your time.
It's okay! We just need to be more passionate!
We've got to put our hearts into it!
I'll try using a different voice!
Didn't think we'd get volunteers that were this serious...
I-it'll be better tomorrow!
Y-yeah...
Though even if it is,
this won't be enough for a report.
There's gotta be something...
Ririsa!
Okay, class!
We've got someone very
special here to read to you!
Hi, everyone! I'm Liliel!
Liliel?!
Whoa!
Liliel!
I watch that on TV!
Aww, thanks.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Nope.
This is a story about Lord Ashford, a brave knight,
and an angel named Liliel.
As long as everyone is still cheering us on,
we'll never give up, ever!
The end.
Liliel-sensei, keep going!
That was fun!
I wasn't sure how they'd react to cosplay,
but this was great!
She had them hooked from
the second she walked in.
Right?
Maybe I should try cosplaying sometime.
I'll lend you one of mine!
Cool, these pictures came out good.
Not sure if this'll work,
but we'll at least be able
to put together a good report.
Ririsa?
Sorry! That sounds good.
I haven't gotten through any of the anime I recorded.
Or even watched anything from last season.
I'm getting left behind...
Eri
Eri?!
Long time no talk.
Sorry.
Why're you apologizing?
Do you remember that girl we saw?
She was at Spring Cosfest.
Riri... You saw her?
Yeah, and she was super cute.
I told her we should meet up at Summer Comiket.
Wow.
Are you going, Mayura?
You haven't worn your masterpiece yet.
I threw it out.
Yeah, right. You'd never do that.
I can't wear it. I'm a teacher now.
But you want to, right?
God, Eri.
Why did I spend so much time on something
too embarrassing to talk about in public?
Mayura...
I still want to cosplay.
But I can't if I want to live my life.
I had way too much last night...
I've got to live my life...
Manga
Club
Good work, you two.
I heard good things about your reading sessions.
Sounds like you've got the report ready, too.
No.
Sensei!
We're not submitting this report!
Do You Love Cosplay?